[
  {
    "question": "Who was the first person to step on moon?",
    "correct_answer": "Neil Armstrong",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Charles Duke", "Buzz Aldrin", "Alan Shepard"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the Indian space agency?",
    "correct_answer": "ISRO",
    "incorrect_answers": ["NASA", "Roscosmos", "JAXA"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately how old is the Universe?",
    "correct_answer": "13.8 billion years",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "1.7 billion years",
      "16.9 billion years",
      "100 million years"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of our galaxy?",
    "correct_answer": "Milky Way",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Andromeda", "Cygnus A", "Magellanic Clouds"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately how far is the Earth from the Sun?",
    "correct_answer": "150 million km",
    "incorrect_answers": ["71 million km", "123 million km", "246 million km"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When was the James Webb Space Telescope launched?",
    "correct_answer": "25 December 2021",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1 January 2022", "20 July 2020", "13 November 2021"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of Elon Musk's aerospace company?",
    "correct_answer": "SpaceX",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Virgin Galactic", "Blue Origin", "Lockheed Martin"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately how much did it cost to build the international space station?",
    "correct_answer": "$150 billion",
    "incorrect_answers": ["$3 billion", "$71 billion", "$233 billion"]
  },
  {
    "question": "When was NASA established?",
    "correct_answer": "29 July 1958",
    "incorrect_answers": ["31 October 1936", "14 March 2002", "30 May 1975"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which was the first satellite launched by the European Space Agency?",
    "correct_answer": "COS-B",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Aryabhata spacecraft",
      "Explorer 1",
      "Dong Fang Hong 1"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "When did Yuri Gagarin go to space?",
    "correct_answer": "April 12, 1961",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "June 5, 1978",
      "December 23, 1999",
      "January 4, 1959"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Who was the first billionaire to go to space?",
    "correct_answer": "Richard Branson",
    "incorrect_answers": ["Jeff Bezos", "Bill Gates", "Yusaku Maezawa"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Approximately how many days does it take for Jupiter to complete one revolution around the Sun?",
    "correct_answer": "4,331 days",
    "incorrect_answers": ["1,348 days", "2,145 days", "3,562 days"]
  }
]
